powtoken.com 2018-02-18

# POWtoken.com Privacy Policy

                    POWtoken.com Privacy Policy
1.    Introduction
1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; in this
      policy we explain how we will treat your personal information.
1.2 By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of
      cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
2.    Credit
2.1 This document was created using a template from SEQ Legal
      (http://www.seqlegal.com).
3.    Collecting personal information
3.1 We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:
      (a)   Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of
            this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser
            type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit,
            page views and website navigation paths);
      (b)   information that you provide to us when registering with our website
            (including your email address);
      (c)   information that you provide when completing your profile on our
            website (including your name, profile pictures, gender, date of birth,
            relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details and
            employment detail);
      (d)   information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our
            email notifications and/or newsletters (including your name and email
            address);
      (e)   information that you provide to us when using the services on our
            website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services
            (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use);
      (f)   information that you post to our website for publication on the internet
            (including your user name, your profile pictures and the content of your
            posts);
      (g)   information contained in or relating to any communication that you
            send to us or send through our website (including [the communication
            content and metadata associated with the communication); and
      (h)   any other personal information that you choose to send to us.
3.2 Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must
      obtain that person's consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that
      personal information in accordance with this policy.

4.     Using personal information
 4.1 Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the
       purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website.
4.2 We may use your personal information to:
       (a)   administer our website and business;
       (b)   personalise our website for you;
       (c)   enable your use of the services available on our website;
       (d)   supply to you services purchased through our website;
       (e)   send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect
             payments from you;
       (f)   send you email notifications that you have specifically requested;
       (g)   send you marketing communications relating to our business [or the
             businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of
             interest to you, by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this,
             by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no
             longer require marketing communications);
       (h)   deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to
             our website;
       (i)   keep our website secure and prevent fraud; and
       (k)   verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of
             our website (including monitoring private messages sent through our
             website private messaging service).
4.3 If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will
       publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the licence you
       grant to us.
4.4 Your privacy settings can be used to limit the publication of your information on
       our website, and can be adjusted using privacy controls on the website.
4.5 We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to
       any third party for the purpose of their or any other third party's direct
       marketing.

5.    Disclosing personal information
5.1 We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers,
      insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as
      reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.
5.2 We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of
      companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all
      its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in
      this policy.
5.3 We may disclose your personal information:
      (a)    to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
      (b)    in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;
      (c)    in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including
             providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention
             and reducing credit risk);
      (d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset
             that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and
      (e)    to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other
             competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where,
             in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably
             likely to order disclosure of that personal information.
5.4 Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information
      to third parties.
6.    International data transfers
6.1 Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred
      between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use
      the information in accordance with this policy.
6.2 Information that we collect may be transferred to the following countries which
      do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European
      Economic Area: the United States of America, Russia, Japan, China and India.
6.3 Personal information that you publish on our website or submit for publication
      on our website may be available, via the internet, around the world. We
      cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.
6.4 You expressly agree to the transfers of personal information described in this
      Section 6.

7.    Retaining personal information
7.1 This Section 7 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are
      designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation
      to the retention and deletion of personal information.
7.2 Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be
      kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
7.4 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 7, we will retain documents
      (including electronic documents) containing personal data:
      (a)    to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
      (b)    if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or
             prospective legal proceedings; and
      (c)    in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including
             providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention
             and reducing credit risk).
8.    Security of personal information
8.1 We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the
      loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
8.2 We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password-
      and firewall-protected) servers.
8.3 All electronic financial transactions entered into through our website will be
      protected by encryption technology.
8.4 You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is
      inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over
      the internet.
8.5 You are responsible for keeping the password you use for accessing our website
      confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to
      our website).
9.    Amendments
9.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our
      website.
9.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any
      changes to this policy.
9.3 We may notify you of changes to this policy [by email or through the private
      messaging system on our website].
10.   Your rights
10.1 You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold
      about you; provision of such information will be subject to:

      (a)    the payment of a fee (currently fixed at USD 10); and
      (b)    the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we
             will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor
             or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current
             address).
        10.2 We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent
              permitted by law.
        10.3 You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal
              information for marketing purposes.
        10.4 In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our
              use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will
              provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal
              information for marketing purposes.
11.   Third party websites
11.1 Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites.
11.2 We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and
      practices of third parties.
12.   Updating information
12.1 Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to
      be corrected or updated.
13.   Cookies
13.1 Our website uses cookies.
13.2 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that
      is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The
      identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a
      page from the server.
13.3 Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent
      cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set
      expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session
      cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the
      web browser is closed.
13.4 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a
      user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the
      information stored in and obtained from cookies.
13.5 We use both session and persistent cookies on our website.

13.5 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many
      websites.
13.7 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our
      website.
13.8 Deleting cookies will have a negative impact on the usability of many
      websites.
14.   Our details
14.1 This website is owned and operated by Bitzza Limited
14.2 We are registered in the UK with company number 10668008
